Hey.
What you working on?
Anything interesting?
Yeah, actually.
I'm-I'm building a new algorithm
that weights search results...
I'm gonna get laid.
Congratulations.
Which hand are you going to use?
That's, uh... that's funny.
Because, um, you know,
if someone were to look
at the two of us,
they'd probably think
I'd be the one sitting home,
on a Friday night
babbling on about
some geek nonsense,
and you'd be the one
going out to,
you know, get laid.
Who's the "lucky lady"?
Lyndsey is the lucky...
getting "laid-y."
Doesn't it bother you
that after she's with you,
she goes home
to her more handsome,
successful boyfriend?
Why? I do the same thing.
How did Lyndsey end up with him?
Well, how did I end up with him?
Hey, Walden.
Hey.
Michaela, Heidi,
Sarah, this is Walden.
He's super hot, super rich
and super single.
These are my friends,
and we are all super high.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
Nice house.
(laughing):
I am so wasted.
What are you guys doing tonight?
Oh, we're gonna play poker.
You want to join?
Yeah, come play with us!
It'll be fun.
I am so wasted.
You know what, I-I actually
have a lot of work to do,
and need to get
to bed early, but...
you guys have fun.
(gasps) We should
play strip poker.
Yes.
All right, ante up.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x04 ♪
Clank, Clank, Drunken Skank
Original Air Date on October 17, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey.
All right,
let's get it over with.
Tell me all the disturbing
details of how you "got laid."
She never showed.
She couldn't get away from
Larry, so I spent half the night
waiting for her
in the parking lot of an ampm.
Wow, I'm actually enjoying
one of your stories.
Please, continue.
But on the plus side,
at 12:01, all the donuts
became half price.
By 12:19, I-I had made friends
with the guy
who lives
in the men's room, Raul.
Is he looking for a roommate?
You laugh, but he actually
turned the changing table
into a Murphy bed.
I'm sorry,
but if I remember correctly,
last night, you were pretty sure
that you were going
to "get laid."
But, in fact,
you didn't "get laid."
Are you done?
Are you done not "getting laid"?
(sighs)
Seriously,
why are you doing this?
Because I get
to have sex with Lyndsey.
But you didn't have sex.
You ended up shame-eating
stale donuts
and talking to a homeless guy
in a men's room.
They were not stale,
and Raul has a name.
You can't let Lyndsey
treat you like this.
You deserve better.
I know.
Raul said the same thing.
Well, I had a great night
last night.
I ended up playing strip poker
with four incredibly
beautiful women.
Oh, yeah,
I've been on that site.
No, it was Jenny
and her friends.
What a sec, is that
the charge on my card
for TexasSqueezeEm.com?
Wait, you played strip poker
with my niece?
She was the dealer.
But she did flop a great pair.
Walden, Jenny is family.
If you cross that line,
I am not gonna be
your friend anymore.
I mean, I'm still
gonna live here,
but I'm not gonna be
your friend anymore.
Relax, it was harmless fun.
JENNY:
Hey!
Look who's got his clothes on.
Uh...
I had clothes on last night.
Yeah, you were wearing a sock.
And not on your foot.
It looked like Santa filled
a stocking
at Elton John's house.
"Harmless fun"?
No, she did not see
Bennie or the Jets.
Hey, we're gonna
hang out again tonight
if you want to join us.
Yeah, sure.
Cool. I'll see you at 11:00.
What, 11:00?
What is it, New Year's Eve?
(laughs)
Bring your sock.
You're not really going out
with them, are you?
Is this about Jenny?
Will you stop it?
I'm not the creepy guy who wants
to sleep with your niece.
I'm the creepy guy
who wants to sleep
with your niece's friends.
And don't you think
that's a little sad?
I mean, a 35-year-old man
hanging out with a bunch
of hot young girls who just want
to drink, party, get naked...
and anything I say
after this point
doesn't really matter, does it?
It doesn't.
I've never had this in my life.
Wh-When I was her age, I'd
already dropped out of M.I.T.,
gotten married
and started my own business.
I was delivering pizza,
going to junior college
and dating a melon.
Oh, God!
I called her my little honeydew.
Walden?
I'm up. Let's party.
Jagerbombs,
bottle service.
What's going on? I thought you
were going out with the girls.
I am, but not until 11:00.
What is it... 9:00?
How can I be so sleepy?
I've already had two naps
and three Red Bulls.
Uh, my brother Charlie had a
great trick for staying awake.
Two hookers and an eight ball.
I'll pass.
What's with the bag?
Oh, my God,
are you moving in with Raul?
No, Lyndsey felt guilty
about last night
and Larry is on a business trip,
so she is treating me
to a romantic rendezvous
at a four-star hotel
at the beach.
Oh, come on, man.
She's treating you
like a piece of meat.
I know, it's great.
Plus, I have already masturbated
so I can hit the sweet spot
between "you're done already?"
and "enough already."
Enough already.
Don't worry, I'll talk to her.
Okay, well, good luck.
And give Lyndsey my best.
Sure, right after
I give her my best.
Boo-ya!
Hi.
Oh, so you did decide
to show up tonight.
I know. Sorry I'm late.
It's fine.
You just turned happy hour
into miffed hour.
And four-dollar pot stickers
into eight-dollar pot stickers.
Well, the important
thing is I'm here now,
and you look really
nice tonight.
Did you do something
different with your hair?
You don't have to flatter me.
You know I'm gonna give it up.
But we do need to talk.
I said I was sorry.
It's not just that;
it's everything.
It's the...
it's the sneaking around,
it's the curt texts,
it's the going Dutch.
Alan, you know this
is complicated.
I have a boyfriend.
Yes, and I have feelings.
And I am feeling disrespected.
I hear you, and
I will work harder
to make sure that you don't
feel taken for granted.
Thank you.
Now, why don't we
go up to our room
and respectfully
disrespect each other?
Ooh, someone wants a spanking.
I know.
Can it be me this time?
Oh, yeah, we can play
naughty school girl
and no-nonsense math teacher.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes, 138 divided
by two is 69.
No.
It's Stephanie Chapman.
Shh. Maybe she
won't see us.
Lyndsey, Alan!
Stephanie, hi.
Oh, wow, uh, l-look at you,
you look great.
I should. I got the Lap-Band,
and I dropped 172 pounds.
Oh.
Good for you.
Hold your applause till the end.
This is the end.
So, what are you two doing here?
Oh, well...
There...
Are you guys back together?
No, no, we're just...
Did you split up with Larry?
No, Alan and I are
just friends and...
Wine, hotel?
(singsongy):
I smell a hookup.
Oh, we are... we are
definitely not together.
Wh-What you smell are
eight-dollar pot stickers.
So, wh-what brings you here?
Uh, there is a singles' mixer,
and this former fatty
is looking for a sugar daddy.
Make sure he's
a-a sugar-free daddy.
(giggles)
You are adorable.
I could just eat you up.
I don't know, I'd probably
just taste like chicken.
Mmm, I'll bring the biscuits
and you bring the gravy.
Okay, I'm gonna leave
you two "friends" alone.
Hashtag "suspicious."
Great seeing you.
You, too.
Oh, take care.
I know you're gonna hate
to see me go,
but you're gonna love
watching me walk away.
Oh, God.
She is the most annoying woman
on the planet.
Yeah, she is horrible.
You have to go
out with her.
Hmm? What?
She totally suspects
we're having an affair.
The only way to convince
her we're not a couple
is for you to ask her out.
No.
Forget her stomach.
They should've stapled
her mouth shut.
That's exactly the problem.
She'll tell Larry.
Oh-oh, no, no, there-there has
to be an easier way.
Can't I just kill her?
It'd be a much smaller grave
to dig now.
I'm serious, if you ever want
to have sex with me again,
you will ask her out.
Oh, fine, fine,
I'll-I'll ask her out.
Now let's go upstairs.
Oh, it's not gonna happen.
She's right over there.
I'm going home.
But-but I thought
we were gonna...
Good-bye.
(huffs)
(laughter, clamoring)
Wow, this is a beautiful house!
Who lives here?
You do.
Whoa, I must be rich!
You are.
Oh, yeah!
Whoa, my fingers are glowing!
I'm so rich I have
rainbow fingers!
Hey, let's get some music going.
Yeah!
Oh!
This is the greatest
song I've ever heard!
Walden? Jenny?
It-it's 3:00
in the morning.
I know, and I'm still awake!
And I'm still wasted!
Oh, no, your fingers
aren't glowing!
Oh, that's because he's poor.
Oh, I am sorry, Alan.
Whoa!
Your skin is so soft.
Guys, feel Alan's skin.
It's so soft.
Whoa!
Okay, okay, okay!
Everybody stop touching me.
Except you.
Hi. I'm Alan.
Alan, I'm high.
What-what is going on?
Oh, Alan, we were at a party,
and we were drinking
and smoking,
and then I ate a tiny pill
off of someone's nipple.
It was like a nipple
Pez dispenser.
Okay, okay, it's time
for the party to end,
and everybody
to just sleep this off.
Yeah, Alan's right.
We should get naked and
go skinny-dipping in the ocean!
Yeah, Sarah's right.
Come on.
(women whooping)
Ha-ha! Yes!
He's going skinny-dipping
with the hot chicks,
and my girlfriend's
banging another dude.
Can you throw me a bone, God?
(thumping nearby)
Oh, I didn't forget
about you, Alan.
There's a new melon
in the fridge.
(chuckles)
Oh, crap.
♪ Men. ♪
Don't be naked, don't be naked.
Damn.
Don't be naked,
don't be naked.
Damn.
Damn!
Whoa!
Whoa.
Morning.
We're naked.
Yes, we are.
How did we get here?
The last thing
I remember
was asking some chick,
"Can you mix these
with alcohol?"
Apparently the answer is no.
Okay, 'cause the...
'cause the last thing I remember
is you looking
in a mirror saying,
"Can we mix these with alcohol""
(laughs)
Don't worry.
Nothing could've happened.
I'm gay.
Ah, that's right.
You're gay.
(laughs)
Wait.
How gay?
Like, one being,
"Yay, it's college!"
Or ten being,
"I'm going Subaru shopping
with Ellen and Rosie."
I'm closer to a nine.
I mean, I make my own soap,
but I don't sell it
at the Lilith Fair.
Oh, great, great.
I mean, granted you're prettier
than a lot of the women
I've dated,
ut you have an outie
and I'm into innies.
Okay, okay,
so we didn't have sex.
That is a load off.
Uh, that's a poor choice
of words.
Although sometimes
I date an innie
who has an outtie in her purse.
What is that supposed to mean?
I don't know,
I'm just saying it's possible.
Oh, God, if Alan finds out,
he's gonna freak out.
He won't move out,
but he will freak out.
Okay, settle down.
We don't even know if there's
anything to freak out about.
(stammers)
Hello.
Stop that!
We got to figure out what to do.
Okay, what we're gonna do
is never talk about this again.
So, you're just saying deny
that we ever woke up
in bed naked together?
I have a motto
for situations like this.
What happens in Jenny,
stays in Jenny.
So, I was really surprised
you called me.
Well, I-I couldn't get
your voice out of my head.
You're not the first one
to say that.
There it goes again.
No, I was surprised
because I was vibing there was
definitely something going on
between you and Lyndsey.
No, we're-we're just friends.
And-and barely that.
She's a drunk, you know?
Oh, believe me, I know.
You should hear wine bottles
in her trash bins
on Friday morning.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, clank, clank,
drunken skank!
Yeah, she's a whore, too.
I don't know
why she ever let you go.
You are quite the catch.
Uh, I know I present that way,
but I'm more catch and release.
Well, I am not releasing.
(high-pitched whoosh)
(clicks tongue)
(laughs)
You are so cute.
Thank you.
Uh, you're not eating your food.
Do you not like Souplantation?
No, I love it,
but since the surgery,
I can't eat a portion
larger than my fist.
But don't worry.
That only applies to food.
How are you still single?
Hey.
So, listen.
Uh, about that thing
that didn't happen...
I have a way to figure out
if it happened.
I'm not peeing on any sticks.
No.
There is a camera in my room.
(sighs)
And that's why
I don't sleep with guys.
It was your dad's.
And that's why I drink.
So we could watch the video back
and know for sure.
Or...
we could erase it
and continue to deny
that anything ever happened.
Play it.
Ah, damn it.
I was sure you were
gonna say erase it.
No, I want to watch it.
It'll be like a quarterback
watching game film.
Only the quarterback's
a lesbian.
And the game's boning a dude.
Exactly.
Okay.
Here we go.
(sighs)
Wait!
Erase it?
No, I want to make popcorn.
So both of my ex-husbands
turned out to be gay.
But the weird thing is...
is after I divorced them,
they both turned straight again.
What are the odds?
Uh, well, this has been great.
Whoa, somebody's fresh.
(laughs)
Come on in.
I would love to take
you up on that,
but, you know,
it's, uh....
6:45...
and, uh, I have
got to go home
and, uh, hit the hay.
Oh, I have hay here.
And I will definitely
let you "hit it."
That is tempting.
Uh, and I am definitely
gonna have to come
to terms with that while
I'm in the monastery.
All right, I get it.
You're making excuses
because you're still
in love with Lyndsey.
God, no, we're-we're
just friends.
Yeah, and I didn't
just fart in your car.
It's fine, okay?
I get it.
I just feel bad
for her boyfriend.
(groans) Wait!
Uh, if-if I was still
in love with Lyndsey,
would I do this?
Wow.
Do that again, but keep
your eyes open and say my name.
(muffled):
Stephanie?
(both grunt)
Are you sure about this?
Because once we see it,
we can't un-see it.
Yeah, worst-case
scenario, it's a video
of two hot people
having sex.
Well, I'm just gonna say...
if I had sex with one Harper
in this house,
thank God it was you.
(groans) Okay.
Oh, this is not
a good start.
♪ Bow chicka bow wow.
Oh, having sex with a guy
in my dad's bed.
Paging Dr. Freud, huh?
You know what?
Let's just go back to denial.
No, wait, wait!
Wait, that is not me.
I don't have a Fred
Flintstone tattoo.
Well, if that's not you,
then who is she?
You're the one
yabba-dabba-doin' her.
I don't know who that is.
God, I love living
at the beach.
Mmm.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
That's Heidi!
You banged Heidi.
Really?
Yes! Good going.
(grunts)
(laughs)
So, how did I end
up in your bed?
I don't... Uh, wait.
Is that you?
Yeah.
Well, who are you with?
Oops, I turned Sarah.
(laughs)
Nice!
Wh-Whoa, who are
those people?
(grunts)
Do you remember the
bonfire on the beach?
Yeah, the Italian
exchange students!
"I no have-ah
the bus fare-ah."
They no have-ah
no pants-ah!
Oh, wow!
Did we invite them
back to the house?
I guess so-- I mean,
that is a big pile of naked.
Oh... oh, man.
Now Heidi's with the guy
that looks like James Franco.
(laughs)
Wait, that is James Franco!
That guy is in everything!
Wait a second,
who am I with now?
Oh, now you're with Sarah.
(laughs)
Turned her back-- wah!
Oh...
that is some
Game of Thrones stuff there.
Yeah, but we
didn't, uh...?
No, I guess not.
Oh, well, maybe.
That is my ass.
No, that's my ass.
Oh.
Is that your arm?
Uh, no, that is my...
BERTA:
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Hanging out.
Okay. So, listen.
Are we all gonna talk about
the orgy we had last night?
What?
Y-You were there?
Hell, yeah.
I banged James Franco.
♪ Men. ♪
I'm so glad
you were able to get away.
I owe you one for going
out with Stephanie.
The only way I got through it...
Mm-hmm.
was by thinking of you.
Through what?
You know, Stephanie.
I took one for the team.
Rather I, uh,
gave one for the team.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
You had sex with her?
Yeah, the second time
was not easy.
Oh, my God!
What? Wasn't I supposed to?
No, you were supposed
to take her out,
go to a movie or something.
Oh, I don't think I could've sat
through a movie with her.
You are unbelievable.
I'm out of here.
B-But I thought we were gonna...
Oh, no. God, no.
But... but...
but you have a boyfriend!
(sighs)
Hello, uh, Stephanie?
Yeah, it-it's Alan.
Uh, turns out, uh,
the doctor read my MRI wrong.
I will be free tonight.
♪ Men. ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man